<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
      <title>www.jmadden.org</title>
   
   <link>http://jmadden.org/</link>
   <description>Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened. -Dr Seuss</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor> Jacob Madden</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
	  <title>Delhi Rickshaw Game</title>
	  <link>http://jmadden.org//casper/2016/03/30/delhi-rickshaw-game/</link>
	  <author>Jacob Madden</author>
	  <pubDate>2016-03-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
	  <guid>http://jmadden.org//casper/2016/03/30/delhi-rickshaw-game/</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>
I recently joined the <a href="http://www.techvalleygamespace.com" target="_blank">Tech Valley Game Space (TVGS)</a> and participated in their first "Shark Tank" event where people present game ideas and the winning pitch gets access to volunteers to create a game over the following month. My pitch of a game idea called <a href="http://www.techvalleygamespace.com/project-night-delhi-rickshaw-shark-tank-2-march-30-2016" target="_blank">"Delhi Rickshaw"</a> was the winning pitch and we spent the last month developing the idea in Unity. It was a lot of fun to have a push towards finally sitting down to learn the essentials of Unity. I was impressed by how easy the engine is to work with and enjoyed coding in C#. The tutorials from Unity like the Tank Tutorial were also very helpful to get up and running and the key aspects of a game.
</p>

<p>
The Delhi Rickshaw game idea came from my time abroad in Southeast Asia. I was fascinated by the different styles of rickshaw in the various cities and wanted to make a game that merged the perspective of the original Grand Theft Auto, the business idea of Lemonade stand and future clones, and the competition and gamification of R.C. Pro-Am.
</p>

<p style="text-align: center;">
<img src="/assets/images/delhi-rickshaw2.png" alt="Delhi Rickshaw" />
</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>


</channel>
</rss>
